Tell me if it now accords.
Marching to the lowest bar.
Thinking less gets you far.
Logic's left behind the trend.
Idiots get to set the end.
Pleasing drown by empty noise.
Common sense replaced by poise.
Blindly led by liars bold.
Truth gets bought and cheaply sold if knowledge is a crime.
Then what's the price we pay?
Dumbing down is trending now Ignorance is bliss they say Critical thought grown away Standing proud to be cliched Hey!
Stips all the rage Hey!
Turn out the page
TV screens blast mindless shows.
Social media feeds the flame.
Fools get famous overnight while Libra collects the dust.
In formation at our fingertips, we choose to stay in the dark.
Celebrating mediocrity, it's daring us to fart.
Dumping down is trending now.
Ignorance is bliss, they say.
Critical thought thrown away.
Extending brow to make me shay.
Hey!
Stupid's all the rage.
Turn out the page.